A checkout can look finished
and still stop a keyboard
user cold. AccessPatch EU turns
that failure into an evidence-backed
patch, then proves the same
journey works. This is the
real synthetic Lattice Supply checkout
on localhost. I open secure
checkout and use only the
keyboard. Every Tab is intercepted
and returned to the invalid
email. Five presses later, focus
has not moved. The payment
control is unnamed, and the
visible error is silent to
assistive technology. Now I run
npm run demo colon verify.
This is genuine process output.
The script resets the fixture,
starts the app, captures before
evidence, writes deterministic proposals, installs
the frozen repair, scans again,
verifies the journey, and restores
the original source bytes. The
evidence pack contains a screenshot,
sanitized DOM and accessibility data,
a keyboard trace, and source
hints. It produces three stable
findings: A P E U
zero zero one and zero
zero two are critical; zero
zero three is serious. External
requests are blocked and stored
form values are scrubbed. For
judges, this path is labeled
deterministic fixture with approval actor
test fixture. It needs no
login and never pretends a
person approved it. Separately, the
interactive workflow runs inside signed-in
Codex. GPT-5.6 proposes bounded candidate
changes, but cannot approve them
or decide whether they pass.
Every edit is limited to
source slash checkout slash CheckoutPage
dot T S X. The
real diff removes the Tab
trap, names the payment action
Confirm and pay forty-two euros,
connects the error with aria
described by, adds alert and
aria live semantics, and focuses
the invalid email. The allowlist
rejects every other file. AccessPatch
replays the same Playwright journey.
Tab advances, the payment action
exposes its name, invalid input
is announced, and a valid
keyboard submission reaches order confirmation.
Deterministic checks, not the model,
decide the outcome. The receipt
is real: two critical and
one serious blocker are resolved,
no new serious or critical
regression appears, keyboard checkout passes,
and the diff stays inside
the approved root. The demo
then restores the broken fixture
byte for byte, keeping the
repository repeatable while the dashboard
retains genuine before and after
evidence. To judge it, run
npm ci, install Playwright Chromium,
then run npm run demo
colon verify. The terminal ends
with AccessPatch verification: pass. This
route needs no OpenAI Platform
API key; the interactive route
uses signed-in Codex. AccessPatch EU
provides technical evidence, not legal
advice, certification, or guaranteed compliance.