A checkout can look finished
and still stop a keyboard
user cold. AccessPatch EU turns
that failure into an evidence-backed
patch, then proves the same
journey works. Here is the
synthetic Lattice Supply checkout. I
start secure checkout using only
the keyboard. The email receives
focus, but every Tab is
intercepted and returned to it.
Five presses later, focus has
not moved. The payment control
is unnamed, and the visible
validation error is silent to
assistive technology. AccessPatch reruns that
exact journey with Playwright and
axe-core. It records the keyboard
trace, DOM and accessibility evidence,
a screenshot, and source hints.
The baseline ends with three
stable blocker IDs, not a
vague checklist. The evidence view
connects each runtime failure to
a source marker: A P
E U zero zero one
for the unnamed control, zero
zero two for repeated focus,
and zero zero three for
the unannounced error. This is
a bounded, synthetic localhost target;
no customer or payment data
leaves the machine. Inside the
signed-in Codex workflow, GPT-5.6 reads
those artifacts and correlates behavior
with the responsible React source.
It proposes the smallest behavioral
changes: add an accessible name,
remove the Tab trap, and
announce validation while returning focus
to the invalid field. Deterministic
tests, not the model, decide
whether the repair passes. Crucially,
nothing is edited yet. AccessPatch
shows the candidate files, intended
behavior, and editable root. A
human must explicitly approve. Only
then may Codex patch source
slash checkout, and an allowlist
rejects any diff outside that
boundary. After approval, the constrained
diff changes only the evidence-backed
behavior. AccessPatch scans again and
replays the original keyboard journey.
This time Tab advances through
the dialog, the payment action
has a useful name, invalid
input is announced, and a
valid keyboard submission reaches order
confirmation. The verification receipt compares
before and after: all three
known critical fixture blockers were
resolved, no new critical axe
finding appeared, the scripted keyboard
checkout completed, and the diff
remained inside the editable root.
Every claim links back to
captured evidence and the approved
source change. I built this
during OpenAI Build Week with
Codex and GPT-5.6: architecture, tests,
scanner, guarded workflow, plugin, dashboard,
and submission tooling. The primary
workflow uses the signed-in Codex
client, so it needs no
OpenAI Platform API key. AccessPatch
EU provides technical remediation evidence,
not legal advice or accessibility certification.